

Smart Contracts Solidity

Python

JavaScript



Libraries/APIs

Web3.js

ethereum.js

Node.js



Education

NIT Karnataka

M.Tech. - Information Security (C.S.E.) 2014 - 2016CGPA - 7.0

NIT Meghalaya

B.Tech - Computer Science and Engineering 2010 - 2014CGPA - 6.91



Canguages

Telugu

Hindi

English



Solving SUDOKU



A Career Gap

Gap (2018-2022)

 Resigned from my position at Oracle for 'UPSC Civil Services Exam' preparation.

Vatti Praveen Kumar

+91 6301478853 in @vattipraveen @VattiPraveen

@_VattiPraveen_

Profile

Blockchain Developer with 2 years of experience in the industry. Worked on WinWin DeFi project. I have a strong background in smart contracts, consensus algorithms, and data structures. I am interested in Blockchain technology applications (DeFi etc), and Information/Network Security. Looking for a job as a Blockchain Developer that will allow me to build the financial system of tomorrow.



Professional Experience

Associate Blockchain Developer

Rapid Innovation □

Oct 2022 - present | Noida, India

- Worked on WinWin (DeFi Lottery).project.
- Wrote multiple smart contracts and test cases for them.
- Got familiar with Hardhat and Git usage.

Blockchain Intern

Rapid Innovation

Jul 2022 - Sep 2022 | Noida, India

• Blockchain networks, Consensus Algorithms, Basic Smart Contracts like ERC20, ERC721, and simple token exchange platforms, etc.

Network Analyst

Oracle India pvt. Ltd.

Jul 2016 - Dec 2017 | Bangalore, India

- Automated the creation of firewall policies for the Oracle Cloud Environment
 - Programming language: python
 - To open communication between applications that are under different subnetworks/Datacenters, appropriate policies are added to the firewall policies list. Automation reduced the policies creation time from weeks(manual) to hours.
- Maintenance of Oracle Cloud Network and network devices

WinWin

It isd a DeFi app where users can earn daily yield and win prizes (lottery) in popular PulseChain assets.

Nov 2022 - Feb 2023

- Did research on multiple PulseChain assets and their staking pools.
- Wrote smart contracts for staking pools and strategies for different tokens.
- Wrote unit and fuzz test cases for the same.

A New Homomorphic Hashing Algorithm to Check Data Integrity in Cloud

2015 - 2016

• Homomorphism enables users to perform operations on encoded data. Hashing is used to verify data integrity. This algorithm uses the best of both homomorphism and the Hash techniques. The algorithm uses matrix multiplication to generate the homomorphic hash, which is used in checking the integrity of data in the cloud.